听力考试正式开始，请看听力部分第一节。
of three A, B, and
第一节。听下面五段对话，每段对话后有一个小题。从题中所给的三个选项中选出最佳选项。听完每段对话后，你都有十。十秒钟的时间来回答有关小题和阅读下一小题，
Read Excuse me, can you tell me how much the shirt is?
每段对话仅读一遍。例如，现在你有五秒钟的时间看试卷上的例题。你将听到以下内容。
Yes, it's 9.15.
你将有五秒钟的时间。将正确答案标在试卷上。衬衫的价格为九磅十五便士，所以你选择
option We have to a parking space.
项，并将其标在试卷上。现在你有五秒钟的时间阅读第。一小题的有关内容。
Let's drive around the block one more time.
Did you say the restaurant has no off -street parking at all?
None. I checked it.
Look, there's a space!
You have to go now, Judy, or you'll miss your flight.
It's an hour's drive to the airport.
I'm leaving. Don't forget to water my flowers.
Just a minute.
Where's my ticket,
Laura, what's in the mailbox?
It's a thank -you note from our neighbor.
They thank us for visiting them last week when the baby was born.
They also invite us to have dinner next Friday.
Are they back home now?
Should be. Good afternoon.
Paper Museum. Hello.
Could you tell me your opening hours for Saturday?
Yeah. We're open from 10 in the morning to 5 in the afternoon.
Thanks. Excuse me, where is the hotel gym, please?
It's on the top floor.
You can take the lift over there.
Do I have to pay extra?
No, sir. You just need to take your room key with you.
Thank The out.
第一节到此结束。第二节，听下面五段对话或独白每段对话或独白后有几个小题。从题中所给的
three A, B, and Listen
三个选项中选出最佳选项。听每段对话或独白前，你将有时间阅读各个小题。题，每小题五秒钟。听完后，各小题将给出五秒钟的作答时间。每段对话或独白读两遍。听下面一段对。对话。回答第六和第七两个小题。现在你有十秒钟的时间阅读这两个小题。
Mr. Wilson, students from Class 2 want to visit the History Museum.
Will it be all right if I take them there this weekend?
How about their revision test?
Are they through with it?
Yes, they are.
In that case, you can go ahead.
Try to finish it within one day.
So that the students still have a whole day to rest on Sunday.
All right. I'll manage.
Mr. Wilson, students from Class 2 want to visit the History Museum.
Will it be all right if I take them there this weekend?
How about their revision test?
Are they through with it?
Yes, they are.
In that case, you can go ahead.
Try to finish it within one day.
So that the students still have a whole day to rest on Sunday.
All right. I'll manage.
Listen Hi, Linda.
听下面一段对话，回答第八至第十三个小题。现在你有十五秒钟的时间阅读这三个小题。
Fancy seeing you here.
How long have you been shopping?
Almost an hour.
I have a lot to buy.
My daughter, Melissa's birthday, is coming.
I'm trying to get her a good gift, but I don't know what to choose.
She seems to have everything she loves.
Yeah, the same as Clara.
We've already had bags of toys she's no longer playing with.
So this year, we didn't buy her material things.
We gave her an experience gift.
What's that? A city pass, with which she can visit twelve different attractions,
including the National History Museum, the Science Museum,
the Zoo, and more.
How much is it?
Fifty dollars per person for a year -long pass.
I bought three for the whole family.
So you can have a different outing every month for the entire year.
What a great idea!
Hi, Linda. Fancy seeing you here.
How long have you been shopping?
Almost an hour.
I have a lot to buy.
My daughter, Melissa's birthday, is coming.
I'm trying to get her a good gift, but I don't know what to choose.
She seems to have everything she loves.
Yeah, the same as Clara.
We've already had bags of toys she's no longer playing with.
So this year, we didn't buy her material things.
We gave her an experience gift.
What's that? A city pass,
with which she can visit twelve different attractions, including the National
History Museum, the Science Museum,
the Zoo, and more.
How much is it?
Fifty dollars per person for a year -long pass.
I bought three for the whole family.
So you can have a different outing every month for the entire year.
What a great idea!
听下面一段对话，回答第十一至第。十三，三个小题。现在你有十五秒钟的时间阅读这三个小题。
Oh, Kevin. I'm preparing a presentation for the city library.
It's about a girl named Tracy Woods.
What's special about her?
It was an amazing story.
She brought specially trained dogs to special education schools and helped children
to build confidence.
She believes that dogs can help children in ways we can't.
Dogs don't judge, and they don't care who you are or what you look like.
But putting dogs into a school?
Aren't they going to mess up the school?
Don't worry. All the dogs are assessed and trained properly.
There are now 40 dogs working with children aged from 6 to 18.
I hope the children love them.
Of course they do.
I've got some pictures.
I'll show them at my presentation tomorrow morning.
Helen? Busy doing anything?
Oh, Kevin. I'm preparing a presentation for the city library.
It's about a girl named Tracy Woods.
What's special about her?
It was an amazing story.
brought specially trained dogs to special education schools and helped children to
build confidence. She believes that dogs can help children in ways we can't.
Dogs don't judge, and they don't care who you are or what you look like.
But putting dogs into a school?
Aren't they going to mess up the school?
Don't worry. All the dogs are assessed and trained properly.
There are now 40 dogs working with children aged from 6 to 18.
I hope the children love them.
Of course they do.
I've got some pictures.
I'll show them at my presentation tomorrow morning.
听下面一段对话，回答第十四至第十七四个小题。现在你有二十秒钟的时间阅读这四。个小题。
Emily, thank you for taking time out of your busy schedule to answer a few
questions. It's my pleasure.
People say you're doing unpaid work in the new season of My Fair Lady.
Is this what the show business has become?
No, not really.
All of my acting in the new season is unpaid, but the crew is paid.
This is to raise money for the post -production of the show.
I notice you've tried many different kinds of Film, TV, and even theatre.
Yeah, that's how I was trained at university.
work on anything that excites me.
Tell us about the six months you recently spent at the workshop of the Film Center.
It was an unbelievable experience, teaching young actors and actresses and working
with some great acting artists.
It was also great to work in various labs such as directors, writers, and so on.
It's very helpful for making you a really well -rounded and active member of the
film and television industry.
Thank you very much, Emily.
We look forward to your new season.
Emily, thank you for taking time out of your busy schedule to answer a few
questions. It's my pleasure.
People say you're doing unpaid work in the new season of My Fair Lady.
Is this what the show business has become?
No, not really.
All of my acting in the new season is unpaid, but the crew is paid.
This is to raise money for the post -production of the show.
I notice you've tried many different kinds of Film, TV, and even theatre.
Yeah, that's how I was trained at university.
I work on anything that excites me.
Tell us about the six months you recently spent at the workshop of the Film Center.
It was an unbelievable experience, teaching young actors and actresses and working
with some great acting artists.
It was also great to work in various labs such as directors, writers, and so on.
It's very helpful for making you a really well -rounded and active member of the
film and television industry.
Thank you very much, Emily.
We look forward to your new season.
听下面一段独白。回。答第十八至第二十三个小题。现在你有十五秒钟的时间阅读这三个小题。
Hi, everyone. This is the monthly meeting of our club.
We've been fortunate to have got good advice from some famous athletes on how to
improve our skills and build up our body.
Today, we'll hear something different.
We're honored to have Emma Wilson here.
Emma is a health expert and lecturer from UBC, the University of British Columbia.
Emma worked for a football team in Manchester,
then for a very successful rugby team in Dublin,
and finally ended up working here in Vancouver.
Emma says it's challenging to be a health expert because people can be easily
influenced by advertisements that lack scientific support.
Also, people aren't willing to change their views about food and nutrition, as there
is so much confusing information online.
It's really important to hear what experts say, and that's why we've invited Emma
here. She isn't going to tell us about everything we should eat, but she will teach
us to make better choices.
Let's welcome Emma Wilson.
Hi, everyone. This is the monthly meeting of our club.
We've been fortunate to have got good advice from some famous athletes on how to
improve our skills and build up our body.
Today, we'll hear something different.
We're honored to have Emma Wilson here.
Emma is a health expert and lecturer from UBC, the University of British Columbia.
Emma worked for a football team in Manchester,
then for a very successful rugby team in Dublin,
and finally ended up working here in Vancouver.
Emma says it's challenging to be a health expert because people can be easily
influenced by advertisements that lack scientific support.
Also, people aren't willing to change their views about food and nutrition, as there
is so much confusing information online.
It's really important to hear what experts say, and that's why we've invited Emma
here. She isn't going to tell us about everything we should eat, but she will teach
us to make better choices.
Let's welcome Emma Wilson.
第二节到此结束。现在你有两分钟的时间。边将试卷上的答案转涂到答题卡上。
Thank you. Thank you.
听力部分到此结束。